I hope you're here to tell me
you've put the Vic on the market.
No.
I was thinking about
a little refurb.
You know, a few more bells and
whistles. Improved lunchtime menu.
Well, when you sell the Vic,
you'll have the money to do
what you want, won't you?
You know what, Max? I am fed up
with you telling me what to do.
What you talking about?
Well, I fully intended to sign
back your share, you know,
if you'd given me time.
But you had to push it too
far, didn't you?
Yeah, yeah... I mean, the things
I did to try and pay you back.
Get to the point, Ian.
I'm not going to sell the Vic.
You what?
In fact, you're not going to get
another penny from me, full stop.
I'm sorry, Ian, have you
had a bang on the head?
Unless you want the whole Square
to find out about your little
affair with Linda Carter.
You ready?
Right, come on.
What's the matter with Daddy?
He's just a bit tired, that's all.
Go on, go.
Veggie, yeah?
Yeah, I thought
I'd better give it a go.
So how many missed calls
was last night, then?
Five, and that was before
I turned my phone off.
They're just excited.
Yeah, I can tell.
Oh, Rainie, can I just finish my
hash brown before we start
talking periods? Is that all right?
Don't be silly.
I'm really sorry about what
happened yesterday.
I overstepped the mark.